Search

Menu

**Privacy Policy**
------------------

Digital Malayali operates the website “Digital Malayali” at [https://en.digitalmalayali.in/](https://en.digitalmalayali.in/). We take your privacy seriously. To better protect your privacy we provide this privacy policy notice explaining the way your personal information is collected and used.

**Collection of Routine Information**

This website track basic information about its visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this website. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

**Cookies**

Where necessary, this website uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

**Advertisement and Other Third Parties**

Advertising partners and other third parties may use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitor activities on this website to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their servers and is subject to their privacy policies. This website has no access or control over these cookies, scripts and/or web beacons that may be used by third parties.

We have included links on this website for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these websites may differ from our own.

Link to the privacy policy of third-party service providers used by the website

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of **2022-05-09** and will remain in effect except concerning any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

**Contact Information**

For any questions or concerns regarding the privacy policy, please send us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://en.digitalmalayali.in/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

This privacy policy page was created by [Arthur Gareginyan](https://github.com/ArthurGareginyan/privacy-policy-template/) and modified/generated by [Free & Open Source Privacy Policy Generator](https://free-privacy-policy-generator.digitalmalayali.in/).

About Us
--------

* Digital Malayali
* Authors

Contact Us
----------

* Advertise with Us
* Feedback

Made with  in Kerala.Copyright © 2022 Digital Malayali.

#### Ad Blocker Detected!!!

We have detected that you are using extensions to block ads. Please support us by disabling this ad blocker. We rely on ad revenue for hosting this website. We promise not to show annoying pop-up ads that hinder user experience!
